Jaron Lifsey

JaronLifsey@gmail.com | 623-498-9313 | website | Phoenix, AZ

Summary

Two years of experience as a software engineer and four as a game software tester. Proficient in C++, Java, and C# with a bachelor's degree in computer science. Seeking a role where I can apply my skills and meaningfully contribute to the organization while growing professionally.

Experience

Software Engineer II - August 2014 to October 2016 (2 years 2 months)

General Dynamics Mission Systems – Scottsdale AZ

Worked on maintaining software for a satellite 3G network in C++ within a Solaris environment. Examples of performed work included:

- Implementing fixes, unit testing, reviewing code, and writing test plans for test team verification of fixed bugs
- Revising version description and installation documentation and creating an installer for a subsystem used at site
- Maintaining and creating new tools to parse and correlate data in logs received daily from the deployed site to detect issues and monitor system health
- Evaluating and assisting with issues found by the test team

Test Associate III - November 2018 to July 2022 (3 years 9 months)

Experis Game Solutions – Tempe AZ

Worked in a highly collaborative environment as a manual tester. Responsibilities consisted of:

- Coordinating with the team to execute test plans and other self-directed testing
- Writing bugs in Azure DevOps and verifying fixes
- Writing task reports summarizing test coverage and results
- Training new members assigned to the same team on project processes and standards

Software Development Engineer in Test (SDET) II - Aug 2022 – Dec 2022 (5 months)

Experis Game Solutions – Tempe AZ

Briefly worked as a developer creating tests and adding functionality to test automation for a game.

Education

Arizona State University – Tempe, AZ GPA: 3.83 – Dean's List 8 Semesters

B.S. Computer Science May 2014